Guide to the photograph album 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref165
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection
February 1929
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Khatib, Hisham, Mr.
Lincoln, Edith
Lincoln, William P.
Lehnert & Landrock
AD.MC.030_ref165
40
213 Photographic Prints
Generally good, some brittle and warped.
An album of postcards of Egypt, from a journey in February 1929, compiled by William P. Lincoln and Edith Lincoln. The album also includes around ten gelatin silver prints, some which feature the crew of the Nile cruise taken, and ephemera such as newspaper clippings, passes to antiquities sites and a bill from the Shepheard's Hotel. The album belongs to the Hisham Khatb Collection.
Box Electronic Records
E-records AD_MC_030_ref165
Content Description
Digital surrogates of an album of postcards of Egypt, from a journey in February 1929, compiled by William P. Lincoln and Edith Lincoln. The album also includes around ten gelatin silver prints, some which feature the crew of the Nile cruise taken, and ephemera such as newspaper clippings, passes to antiquities sites and a bill from the Shepheard's Hotel.
This album is part of the Hisham Khatib Collection of igital surrogates of 2,930 photographs and postcards (both individual prints and contained within albums) focused on the Near East, including the Holy Land, Palestine, Jordan, Turkey, Syria and Egypt as well as a very small number from Europe.
Photographic Prints; Egypt; Sudan; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Postcards; Travel; Khatib, Hisham, Mr.; Thomas Cook and Son Ltd
- 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165; Lincoln, Edith; Lincoln, William P. (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_MC_030_ref165)
  Egypt; Sudan; Nile River; Boats/Ships; Travel; Postcards
  - The front cover of the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection, featuring an image of the entrance to the tomb of Tutankhamun (KV62) in Thebes and the arms of the cities of London and Paris., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000001_000001; Unknown (Box Electronic Records)
    English Writing; Printed Materials; Egypt; Medals/Insignia; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Postcards; Photographic Prints
  - The inside front cover of the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000002_000001; Unknown (Box Electronic Records)
    Egypt; Sudan
  - A blank page in 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000003_000001; Unknown (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: [Form No. 439] A disembarkation card granted in Port Said. Bottom: A blank arrival card issued by the Egyptian government., 1927; AD_MC_030_ref165_000004_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; English Writing; French Writing; Identity; Government; Travel; Port Said, Egypt
  - Top: a postcard of women leading a herd of goats. Bottom: A postcard of women gathering water and washing clothes in a village surrounded by palm trees., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000005_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Streets/Roads; Palm Trees; Animals; Goats; Children; Countryside/Rural; Water; Men; Pottery; Egypt; Rivers
  - Three postcards. Top: The Qasr el Nil Bridge in Cairo. Middle: Men and women at an oasis. Bottom: a landscape of an oasis., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000006_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Bridges; Statues/Sculptures; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Men; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Animals; Transportation; Hats; Streets/Roads; Cairo, Egypt; Camels; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes; Group Portraits; Postcards; Oases; Donkeys; Police; Uniforms; Street Lamps; Workers; Signs/Signposts
  - Top: A newspaper clipping from The Egyptian Mail detailing the arrivals at Shepheard's Hotel. Bottom: A postcard of Shepheard's Hotel, Cairo., Feb 15, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000007_000001; Lehnert & Landrock; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Newspaper Clippings; Newspapers/Magazines; English Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Hotels; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Street Lamps; Signs/Signposts; Aswan, Egypt; Budapest, Hungary; England, UK; London, England, UK; United States of America; Travel; Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; Printed Materials
  - Two postcards. Top: The interior of Shepheard's Hotel showing The Moorish Lounge. Bottom: The garden at Shepheard's Hotel., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000008_000001; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Furnishings; English Writing; Lanterns/Lamps; Carpets/Rugs; Hotels; Gardens; Palm Trees; Hotels; Printed Materials
  - Top: William. P. Lincoln's bill from the Shepheard's Hotel. Bottom: The cover of an illustrated guide map of the Nile issued by the Tourist Development Association of Egypt., 16 February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000009a_000001; Lehnert & Landrock; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Hotels; Maps; English Writing; Signatures; Travel; Money; Cairo, Egypt
  - The inside of the illustrated guide map of the Nile issued by the Tourist Development Association of Egypt (linked Ref165_000009b)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000009b_000001; Lehnert & Landrock; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Maps; Printed Materials; Nile River; Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Rivers; Water; Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Temples; Tombs/Mausoleums; Dams/Barrages; Buildings; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Aswan, Egypt; Luxor, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Bridges; Agriculture/Farms; Machines; Irrigation; Boats/Ships; Workers; Men; Group Portraits; Oases; Citadel, Cairo, Egypt; Mosques; Religious Sites; Pyramids; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Port Said, Egypt; Monuments/Memorials
  - Two postcards of the Great Pyramids of Giza, the top postcard includes the Great Sphinx of Giza., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000010_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Giza, Egypt; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Deserts; Landscapes; Statues/Sculptures; Deserts; Agriculture/Farms
  - A postcard of square columns in The Valley Temple of Pharaoh Khafre., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000011_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Buildings; Architecture
  - Top: a pamphlet from the Egyptian Museum [Museum of Cairo] featuring a wooden statuette of Ka-Aper, known as Sheikh el-Beled. Bottom: Two postcards. Left: A bronze statue of Pepi I. Right: A statue of Ti, Old Kingdom. From The Mastaba of Ti at Saqqara. Dynasty 5, during the reign of Nuiserre 2416-2392 BC., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000012_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Museums; Statues/Sculptures; Cairo, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Printed Materials; Postcards
  - Three postcards from the Egyptian Museum [Museum of Cairo]. Top: Wooden models of soldiers of Mesehti, Egyptian Pikemen, Middle Kingdom, 11th Dynasty. Bottom Left: A statue of Senusret. Bottom Right: A statue of Amenhotep, son of Hapu., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000013_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Statues/Sculptures; Museums; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Weapons
  - Three postcards from the Egyptian Museum [Museum of Cairo]. Top: A statue of the dwarf Khnumhotep. Bottom Left: A statue of Khaiya, the keeper of the funerary Temple of Ramses II. Bottom Right: A statue of an Egyptian family., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000014_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Museums; Cairo, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Three postcards from the Egyptian Museum [Museum of Cairo]. Top: Wooden busts. Bottom Left: A statue of the priest Ranefer. Bottom Right: A snake sculpture on the lid of a box from a temple of Aesculapius., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000015_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Museums; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Animals
  - Two antiquities site passes labeled "Service Des Antiquites De L'Egypte" (Egypt Antiquities Service)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    - Two antiquities site passes labeled "Service Des Antiquites De L'Egypte" (Egypt Antiquities Service)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000016a_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Travel
    - The inside of the entry tickets to the Egyptian monuments labeled "Service Des Antiquites De L'Egypte" (Egypt Antiquities Service), signed by William and Edith Lincoln., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000016b_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Signatures; Travel; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egypt
    - The inside of the antiquities site passes labeled "Service Des Antiquites De L'Egypte" (Egypt Antiquities Service)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000016c_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Travel; Printed Materials; Postal Stamps; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egypt
  - A map of the Nile River between Luxor, Aswan and Halfa., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000017_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Maps; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Aswan, Egypt; Luxor, Egypt; Wadi Halfa, Sudan; Railways; Transportation; Streets/Roads; Printed Materials; Edfu, Egypt; Thebes, Egypt; Dendera, Egypt
  - A map of the upper Nile River between the Mediterranean and Qena, showing Alexandria and Port Said., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000018_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Maps; Rivers; Water; Printed Materials; Railways; Transportation; Streets/Roads; Alexandria, Egypt; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Port Said, Egypt; Qena, Egypt; Dendera, Egypt; Giza, Egypt; El-Qantara el-Sharqîya, Egypt; Asyut, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt
  - Thomas Cook and Son, Nile Navigation Dept. Steamer booklet and passenger's bill., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    - A handdrawn sketch map of the Nile River Valley, including various monuments., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019a_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Maps; Printed Materials; Nile River; Rivers; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Monuments/Memorials; Egypt; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Alexandria, Egypt; Cairo, Egypt; Port Said, Egypt; Ismailia, Egypt; Suez, Egypt; Saqqara, Egypt; Minia, Egypt; Asyut, Egypt; Edfu, Egypt; Aswan, Egypt
    - A view of a steamer on the Nile River named 's.s. Damietta.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019b_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Photographic Prints; Printed Materials; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Egypt; Forest/Woodlands
    - A diagram/plan of the Nile steamer, Rosetta's, three decks (promenade, upper, and main)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019c_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Boats/Ships; Egypt; Nile River; Rivers; Transportation; Egypt
    - The title page for the 'Schedule of Mileage from Cairo to Aswan.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019d_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Aswan, Egypt; Cairo, Egypt; Nile River; Rivers; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Travel
    - The first page for the 'Schedule of Mileage from Cairo to Aswan.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019e_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Cairo, Egypt; Aswan, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Travel
    - The last page for the 'Schedule of Mileage from Cairo to Aswan.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019f_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Cairo, Egypt; Aswan, Egypt; Travel
    - Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks. A page entitled Baksheesh that urges Nile steamer passengers to avoid donating money to villagers along the Nile., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019g_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Nile River; Rivers
    - William Lincoln's passenger bill from the Nile steamer 'Damietta', issued by Thos. Cook & Son (Egypt) Ltd. Nile Navigation Department., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000019h_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Signatures; Boats/Ships; Travel; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Alcohol; Money
  - The title page from a pamphlet entitled 'Egypt and The Nile, Palestine, Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco' by George Lunn, including a colorized image of people in the desert, one rides a camel., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000020_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Deserts; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Men; Group Portraits; Camels; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Children; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Nile River; Rivers; Palestine; Algeria; Tunisia; Morocco
  - A clipping of the Pyramid of Djoser in Saqqara, with the text "Egypt Memphis and Sakkara.", February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000021_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Memphis, Egypt; Saqqara, Egypt; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Printed Materials
  - Top: (No. 1132) Sakkara - The Step Pyramid (a postcard of two men in front of the Pyramid of Djoser). Bottom: (No. 1133) The Step Pyramid seen from the Sycomore (the Pyramid of Djoser seen at a distance)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000022_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Saqqara, Egypt; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Deserts; Donkeys; Men; Streets/Roads; Oases; Landscapes; Animals; Group Portraits
  - Top: (No. 1134) Sakkara - The Pyramids of Dashur (a postcard of a canal and fields with the Bent Pyramid (Pyramid of Sneferu) in the background). Bottom Left: (No. 1135) Sakkara -Tomb of Ptahotep - Mural Decoration (a relief in the Tomb of Ptahhotep). Bottom Right: (No. 1136) Sakkara - Tomb of Ti Mural - Mural Painting (a mural painting in the Tomb of Ti)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000023_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Deserts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Paintings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Tombs/Mausoleums; Water; Saqqara, Egypt; Agriculture/Farms
  - Top: Memphis - The Colossal Statue of Rameses II (a postcard of the Colossal Statue of Ramesses II in Memphis). Bottom: (No. 1130) Memphis - The Colossal Statue of Rameses II (Detail) (a boy crouching beside the statue of the Colossal Statue of Ramesses II)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000024_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Boys; Children; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palm Trees; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Memphis, Egypt; Individual Portraits
  - Top: Memphis - The Colossal Statue of Rameses II (a postcard of the Colossal Statue of Ramesses II in Memphis). Bottom: Memphis - Head of the Statue of Rameses II (a postcard of a boy with the head of Statue of Ramesses II)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000025_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Boys; Children; Memphis, Egypt; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palm Trees; Horses; Animals; Signs/Signposts
  - Two postcards labeled 'Memphis - The alabaster Sphinx' (the Sphinx of Memphis)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000026_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Memphis, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Camels; Animals; Palm Trees; Landscapes
  - A close view of the Sphinx of Memphis., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000027_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palm Trees; Memphis, Egypt; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes
  - Top: A clipping with the text 'Upper-Egypt Abidos-Denderah' with a view of the Temple of Dendera. Bottom: A clipping with a detailed view of the birth house of Horus at the Temple of Dendera., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000028_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Dendera, Egypt; Temples; Architecture; Buildings; Printed Materials
  - Cook's Nile Services booklet and promotional material, February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000029_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    - The passenger list for the Nile steamer, s.s. 'Damietta' in a Cook's Nile Services booklet., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000029a_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Nile River; Rivers; Egypt
    - A printed cartoon on a Cook's Nile Services booklet by Tony Binder of silhouettes of people by the banks of the Nile. A man riding a donkey, two women carrying jars on their heads and a child., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000029b_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Photographic Prints; Donkeys; Animals; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Children; Nile River; Rivers; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
    - The passenger list for the Nile steamer, s.s. 'Damietta' in a Cook's Nile Services booklet., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000029c_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Nile River; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Printed Materials; Travel; Rivers; Luxor, Egypt; Aswan, Egypt; Asyut, Egypt
    - An advertisement for the tourist steamer 'Thebes.', February 25, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000029d_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
      Printed Materials; Travel; Sudan; Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Rivers; Nile River
  - Top: Three portraits of men on the steamer, s.s. 'Damietta'. Bottom: a group portrait of the s.s. 'Damietta's' crew., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000030_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Egypt; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Workers; Uniforms; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Group Portraits; Turbans; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Clocks/Watches
  - A blank page in 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000031_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1560) Abydos: The famous Liste of the Kings (the Abydos King List). Bottom Left: (No. 1556) Abydos: The Temple of Sethos (a postcard of a man in the Temple of Sethos). Bottom Right: (No. 1559) Pillars of the Temple (a postcard of pillars in the Temple of Sethos)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000032_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Temples; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Hats; Luxor, Egypt
  - Three postcards. Top: Abydos: Sethos offering to the Sacred Boats (a relief in the Temple of Sethos depicting Sethos' offering of the sacred boats). Bottom Left: (No.1566) Denderah: The Temple of the Goddess Hathor. Bottom Right: Abydos: Part of the Temple of Sethos I (a man sitting at the base of a column in the Temple of of Sethos I)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000033_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures; Turbans; Hats
  - Three postcards. Top: A view of the town, El Araba El Madfuna. Bottom Left: (No. 1565) Ptolomey offering to Hathor. Bottom Right: (No. 1567) A view of the Temple of Hathor within the Dendera Temple Complex., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000034_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Countryside/Rural; Agriculture/Farms; Palm Trees; Egypt; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Donkeys; Animals; Men; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Dendera, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Top: A view of the Great Vestibule of the Temple of Hathor. Bottom: (No. 1564) A relief in the Dendera Complex of Ptolomey offering to Isis and Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000035_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Dendera, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures
  - Top: (No. 1562) A postcard view of the Temple of Hathor. Bottom: a view of an ancient Egyptian relief., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000036_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Dendera, Egypt; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Deserts; Buildings; Architecture; Statues/Sculptures